Guide to the McKim Mead and White Architectural Records circa 1875-1950 PR 42
New-York Historical Society
- Series III: Specifications
  - Pennsylvania Station, Cooking apparatus and equipment (Offsite-box III.46, Folder 7)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Electrical Fixtures (Offsite-box III.46, Folder 8)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Floor Work (Offsite-box III.46, Folder 9)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Escalators (Offsite-box III.47, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania Station, General Construction (Offsite-box III.47, Folder 2)
  - Pennsylvania Station, General Construction (Offsite-box III.47, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Granite Work (Offsite-box III.47, Folder 4)
  - Pennsylvania Station and Boiler House, Harrison and Newark, NJ (Offsite-box III.47, Folder 5)
  - Pennsylvania Station and Boiler House, Harrison and Newark, NJ (Offsite-box III.47, Folder 6)
  - Pennsylvania Station and Boiler House, Harrison and Newark, NJ (Offsite-box III.48, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Interior Stone (Offsite-box III.48, Folder 2)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Iron Work (Offsite-box III.48, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Marble Work (Offsite-box III.48, Folder 4)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Newark, NJ (Offsite-box III.48, Folder 5)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Newark, NJ (Offsite-box III.49, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Newark, NJ (Offsite-box III.49, Folder 2)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Offices and Stores (Offsite-box III.49, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Plumbing (Offsite-box III.49, Folder 4)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad Station, Pittsburg, PA (Offsite-box III.50, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Steelwork (Offsite-box III.50, Folder 2)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Limestone and Tile Work (Offsite-box III.50, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Waterproofing and Fireproofing (Offsite-box III.50, Folder 4)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Woodwork (Offsite-box III.50, Folder 5)
  - Phillips D.C., Washington D.C. (Offsite-box III.50, Folder 6)
  - Porchester Library, Porchester NY (Offsite-box III.50, Folder 7)
  - Public School #4, Brooklyn, NY (Offsite-box III.50, Folder 8)
  - Public School #4, Brooklyn, NY (Offsite-box III.51, Folder 1)
  - Public School #4, Brooklyn, NY (Offsite-box III.51, Folder 2)
  - Plymouth Rock and Pilgrim Hall (Offsite-box III.51, Folder 3)
  - Radcliffe College (Offsite-box III.51, Folder 4)
  - Racquet and Tennis Club, Park Avenue, NY (Offsite-box III.51, Folder 5)
  - Racquet and Tennis Club, Park Avenue, NY (Offsite-box III.52, Folder 1)
  - Racquet and Tennis Club, Park Avenue, NY (Offsite-box III.52, Folder 2)
  - Redmond Johnston, Trivoli, NY (Offsite-box III.52, Folder 3)
  - Redmond Johnston, Trivoli, NY (Offsite-box III.52, Folder 4)
  - Rhode Island, State House (Offsite-box III.52, Folder 5)
  - Rochester Savings Bank (Offsite-box III.52, Folder 6)
  - Rumsey (Offsite-box III.52, Folder 7)
  - Saint-Gaudens, Augustus, Memorial (Offsite-box III.53, Folder 1)
  - Saint Peter's Church, Morristown (Offsite-box III.53, Folder 2)
  - Savoy Plaza Hotel, NY (Offsite-box III.53, Folder 3)
  - Savoy Plaza Hotel, NY (Offsite-box III.53, Folder 4)
  - Schenectady City Hall, NY (Offsite-box III.54, Folder 1)
  - Schenectady City Hall, NY (Offsite-box III.54, Folder 2)
  - Seabreeze Hospital, Rockaway Point, NY (Offsite-box III.54, Folder 3)
  - Skinner, Mr. Joseph A., Monument (Offsite-box III.54, Folder 4)
  - Stapleton House, Sir Ronald C. Lindsay (Offsite-box III.54, Folder 5)
  - Sterling, John W. Esquire, Mausoleum (Offsite-box III.54, Folder 6)
  - Taylor, H.A.C. (Offsite-box III.54, Folder 7)
  - Tennessee War Memorial, Nashville, TN (Offsite-box III.55, Folder 1)
  - Tiffany Building Addition, 391 5th Avenue, NY (Offsite-box III.55, Folder 2)
  - Tiffany and Company Building, NY (Offsite-box III.55, Folder 3)
  - Tiffany and Company Garage (Offsite-box III.55, Folder 4)
  - The League for Political Education (Offsite-box III.55, Folder 5)
  - The Pacific Mills, 261 5th Avenue, NY (Offsite-box III.56, Folder 1)
  - "The Oaks" at Washington D.C. (Offsite-box III.56, Folder 2)
  - Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority, NY (Offsite-box III.56, Folder 3)
  - Trinity College, Chemistry Building, CT (Offsite-box III.56, Folder 4)
  - Trinity College, Chemistry Building, CT (Offsite-box III.56, Folder 5)
  - Trinity College, Cook Dormitories, CT (Offsite-box III.56, Folder 6)
  - Trinity College, Cook Dormitories, CT (Offsite-box III.56, Folder 7)
  - Trinity College, Field House, CT (Offsite-box III.57, Folder 1)
  - Trinity College, Field House, CT (Offsite-box III.57, Folder 2)
  - Trinity College, Field House, CT (Offsite-box III.57, Folder 3)
  - Tufts College, Dormitories, Posner Hall, Boston, MA (Offsite-box III.57, Folder 4)
  - Tufts College, Dormitories, Posner Hall, Boston, MA (Offsite-box III.57, Folder 5)
  - Twombly, H. Mck. Esquire Residence, Madison, NJ (Offsite-box III.57, Folder 6)
  - Twombly, H. Mck. Esquire Residence, Madison, NJ (Offsite-box III.58, Folder 1)
  - Twombly, H. Mck. Esquire Residence, Madison, NJ (Offsite-box III.58, Folder 2)
  - University Club, NY (Offsite-box III.58, Folder 3)
  - University Club, NY (Offsite-box III.59, Folder 1)
  - University Club, NY (Offsite-box III.59, Folder 2)
  - University Club, NY (Offsite-box III.59, Folder 3)
  - University of Connecticut, Dormitories (Offsite-box III.59, Folder 4)
  - University of Connecticut, Dormitories (Offsite-box III.60, Folder 1)
  - University of Connecticut, Dormitories (Offsite-box III.60, Folder 2)
  - University of Pennsylvania, Wharton School Building (Offsite-box III.60, Folder 3)
  - University of Rochester, Memorial Art Gallery, NY (Offsite-box III.60, Folder 4)
  - University of Vermont (Offsite-box III.60, Folder 5)
  - University of Vermont, Southwick Memorial (Offsite-box III.60, Folder 6)
  - University of Vermont, IRA Allen Chapel (Offsite-box III.61, Folder 1)
  - University of Vermont, Women's Dormitory (Offsite-box III.61, Folder 2)
  - Washington Heights, Educational Building, NY (Offsite-box III.61, Folder 3)
  - Wesleyan University, Biological Laboratory (Offsite-box III.61, Folder 4)
  - Wesleyan University, Downey House (Offsite-box III.61, Folder 5)
  - Wesleyan University, Gymnasium (Offsite-box III.61, Folder 6)
  - Wesleyan University, Hall Laboratory of Chemistry (Offsite-box III.61, Folder 7)
  - Wesleyan University, Harriman Hall (Offsite-box III.61, Folder 8)
  - Wesleyan University, Indoor Field (Offsite-box III.62, Folder 1)
  - Wesleyan University, Middletown, CT (Offsite-box III.62, Folder 2)
  - Wesleyan University, Olin Memorial Library (Offsite-box III.62, Folder 3)
  - Wesleyan University, Steps and Terraces (Offsite-box III.62, Folder 4)
  - Wesleyan University, Squash Court Building (Offsite-box III.62, Folder 5)
  - White House, Washington D.C. (Offsite-box III.62, Folder 6)
  - White, Stanford. Esquire Residence (Offsite-box III.62, Folder 7)
  - Whitney, W.C., Long Island (Offsite-box III.63, Folder 1)
  - Whitney W.C., City House, NY (Offsite-box III.63, Folder 2)
  - Willard, Joseph E., NY (Offsite-box III.63, Folder 3)
  - Willard, Joseph E., Richmond, VA (Offsite-box III.63, Folder 4)
  - Women's Golf and Tennis Club, Glen Head, LI (Offsite-box III.63, Folder 5)
  - 8th East 56th Street, NY (Offsite-box III.63, Folder 6)
- Series IV: Photographs, circa 1880s-1960s
  The Photographs series includes copy photos of architectural drawings, glass plate negatives, printed material (offprints from publications, entire publications, postcards), newspaper clippings, documents from Departments of Documents and Buildings (generally for New York City projects), handwritten notes, and sometimes correspondence or blueprints. (This series does not include photo albums; see Series V for those, along with scrapbooks.)
  All folders contain photographs unless otherwise specified. For projects that have multiple folders of material, general descriptions of what is in each folder have been given. Projects that merely have a listing of their name are represented by a folder of photographs only.
  Sometimes images of other buildings may appear in a specific project's file. These were found with the other photographs in the file, and often cases have manuscript notations on them to "file in [project name]". They were most likely used as models for buildings, or contained elements or ideas that were to be incorporated into the project in question.
  Photographers included are Blackman Photo Service, Edwin J. Cardswell, Louis H. Dreyer, Gottscho-Schleisner, H. Ernest King, Schuyler Carteret Lee, J.C. Maugans, C. Ording, Richard Averill Smith, Adolph Studly, Tebbs Architectural Photos, Irving Underhill, United States Army Signal Corps, DeWitt Ward, and Wurts Bros.
  The files of photographic prints and any related materials are housed and organized by size, and arranged in alphabetical order within each size. These are followed by a set of glass plate negatives. Because of this size-oriented arrangement, a particular subject can be found in more than one subseries.
  Subseries IV.A. Small Photographs
  Subseries IV.B. Medium Photographs
  Subseries IV.C. Large Photographs
  Subseries IV.D. Glass Negatives
  - Subseries IV.A: Small Photographs, 1885-1956 (bulk, undated)
    This subseries includes photograph files housed upright in 42 document boxes. The majority of these photographs are 8 x 10, but they also include small snapshots.
    - Abbey, Francis Maria. Captain Thomas Abbey Memorial, Enfield, CT (Offsite-box 1)
      Photo; Publication
    - Adams, Edward Dean, Residence, Rumson, NJ (Offsite-box 1)
      Newspaper Clippings
    - Adams, Henry Monument in Rock Creek Cemetery, Washington, DC (Offsite-box 1)
      Printed Material
    - Adams, Josephine M., Residence, 360 East 50th St., New York, NY, 1925 (Offsite-box 1)
      Department of Buildings Documents
    - Adelphi College, Garden City, NY, 1929-1944 (Offsite-box 1)
      Administrative Building (1929, undated); Classroom Building (1929, undated); Nurse Training Dorms; Recreation Building; Printed Material and Newspaper Clippings (1935-1944)
    - Adirondack Power and Light Corporation, Amsterdam, NY, 1920 (Offsite-box 1)
      Powerhouse and Crib House (1920); General
    - Alden, R. Perry, Residence, Cornwall, PA (Offsite-box 1)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 629-635 W. 155th St., New York, NY, 1921-1923 (Offsite-box 1)
      Construction Photos (1921-22); Bronze Door Photos; Copies of Renderings and Plans; Department of Buildings Documents (1921-23); Printed Material
    - American Academy in Rome, Rome, Italy, 1922-1939 (Offsite-box 1)
      Photos; Printed Material (1922-39)
    - American Battle Monuments Commission (Box 1 of 2) (Offsite-box 1)
      Brookwood American Cemetery, Brookwood, England; Flanders Fields American Cemetery, Flanders Fields, Belgium; Waereghem American Cemetery, Waereghem, Belgium
    - American Battle Monuments Commission (Box 2 of 2) (Offsite-box 2)
      Aisne-Marne American Cemetery, Belleau, France: Photos, Copy of ground plan; Somme American Cemetery, Bony, France: Photos, Copy of ground plan; Oise-Aisne American Cemetery, Fere-en-Tardenois, France; American War Memorial, Fismes, France: Photos, Maps; Meuse-Argonne American Cemetery, Romagne-sous-Montfaucon, France; Suresnes American Cemetery, Suresnes, France; St. Mihiel American Cemetery, Thiaucourt, France; American Military Cemetery, Florence, Italy: Photos of ground plans and other plans
    - American University in Beirut, Lebanon (Offsite-box 2)
      Aerial and General Photos; College Hall
    - American War Memorial, Rome, Italy (Offsite-box 2)
      Photos; Copies of renderings
    - Amherst Club, 273-275 Lexington Ave., New York, NY, 1929-1939 (Offsite-box 2)
      Department of Buildings Documents (1929); Newspaper Clippings (1937-39)
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA (Box 1 of 3) (Offsite-box 2)
      General Photos; Building and Landscape Photos; Athletic Complex; Baseball Cage; Chemistry Building; College Hall; Converse Memorial Library: Construction and Exterior Photos
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA (Box 2 of 3) (Offsite-box 3)
      Converse Memorial Library, cont'd: Interior Photos, Copies of floor plans and 3D models, Printed Material; Derose House (1946-48); Dormitories; Hospital and Infirmaries; James and Sterns Halls; Johnson Chapel: Photos, Copies of renderings; Kirby Memorial Theater; Little Red School; Lord Jeffery Inn; Mead Art Museum: Exterior and Interior Photos, Copies of renderings, Art Collection
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA (Box 3 of 3) (Offsite-box 4)
      Octagon House; Pratt Gymnasium; Sculpture Photos; Stearns Church; Theater; Valentine Hall; White House or Faculty House; Williston Hall; Copies of Plans, renderings, grounds plans; Printed Material (1931-40); Publications
    - Anacostia River Bridge, Washington, DC, 1938-1939 (Offsite-box 5)
    - Appleton Residence, Lenox, MA (Offsite-box 5)
    - Aquarium (Addition), Battery Park, New York, NY, 1922 (Offsite-box 5)
      Department of Buildings Documents (1922)
    - Arlington Memorial Bridge Commission, Washington, DC, 1926-1941 (Offsite-box 5)
      Arlington Memorial Bridge: Construction Photos (1927-28); Completion Photos; Parkway approach to Lincoln Memorial (1927); Plaza Watergate; Quarry Photos; Sculpture: General, Equestrian Monument Models; Copies of renderings; Newspaper Clippings (1934-41); Printed Material; Publication (1926)
    - Arlington National Cemetery, Arlington, VA (Offsite-box 6)
      Photos; Niche Photos; Copies of renderings
    - Arnold, B.W., Residence, Albany, NY (Offsite-box 6)
    - Astor, J.J., Casino, Rhinebeck, NY (Offsite-box 6)
    - Atterbury, Boudinot, Residence (Alteration), Seabright, NJ (Offsite-box 6)
    - Ballantine Residence, Morris Plains, NJ (Offsite-box 6)
    - Bank of Buffalo, Buffalo, NY, 1924 (Offsite-box 6)
      Construction photos (1924); Completion photos (1924); Images of 3-dimensional models; Printed Material
    - Bank of Montreal, Canada (general and unidentified branches) (Offsite-box 6)
      Centennial Coin; Copies of renderings; Sculpture photos
    - Bank of Montreal, Montreal, Canada (Offsite-box 6)
      Exterior and Interior Photos
    - Bank of Montreal, Winnipeg, Canada, 1922-1941 (Offsite-box 6)
      Memorial Statue and Exterior photos; Interior Photos; Copies of renderings; Printed Material (1922-41)
    - Bank of Montreal, Wall Street, NYC, 1927 (Offsite-box 6)
    - Barnard College, New York, NY, 1921-1939 (Offsite-box 6)
      Exterior and Interior photos; Brooks Hall; Library; Department of Buildings Documents (1921-30); Printed Material (1925-39)
    - Barnes, James, Residence, Princeton, NJ (Offsite-box 6)
    - Barney, Mrs. Charles Tracy, Townhouse, 67 Park Avenue, New York, NY (Offsite-box 6)
    - Barrington School, Great Barrington, M.A. (Offsite-box 6)
    - Beard, Mrs. A.M., Residence, Tuxedo, NY (Offsite-box 6)
    - Bell, Isaac Jr., Residence, Newport, RI (Offsite-box 7)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY (Box 1 of 2), 1919-1940 (Offsite-box 7)
      Construction photos (1924-37); Aerial and Exterior Photos; Copies of renderings, elevations and 3-dimensional models; Bureau of Fire Prevention Documents (1926-28); Department of Buildings Documents (1927-40); Printed Material (1910-40)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY (Box 2 of 2), 1919-1940 (Offsite-box 8)
      Administration Building: Construction Photos (1938-1940), Copies of floor plans and elevations; Catholic Chapel; Garage: Copies of floor plans and mechanical drawings; Nurses' Training School: Board of Standards and Appeals Documents (1919), Bureau of Fire Prevention Documents (1919-24), Department of Buildings Documents (1919-24); Out Patient Building and Female Dormitory: Photos, Bureau of Fire Prevention Documents (1926-27), Department of Buildings Documents (1925-30)
    - Bennett, James Gordon Jr., New York Herald Building, New York, NY (Offsite-box 7)
      Printed Material and Correspondence
    - Bennett, T.G., Residence, New Haven CT (Offsite-box 8)
    - Bethlehem Steel Company, Bethlehem, PA, 1954 (Offsite-box 9)
      General; Bethlehem Hotel: Construction Photos, Hotel and Surroundings Photos (1954)
    - Billings, Robert Charles, Portrait Medallion (Offsite-box 9)
    - Blair, Edward Tyler, Residence, Chicago, IL, 1915 (Offsite-box 9)
      Printed Material (1915)
    - Bliss, Mrs. Robert W., Residence, Washington, DC (Offsite-box 10)
      Exterior and Interior Photos; Sculpture and Decorative Furniture
    - Bon Air Hotel, Augusta, GA, 1922-1923 (Offsite-box 10)
      Construction and Interior Photos; Exterior Photos (1922); Copies of renderings; Printed Material (1923, undated)
    - Booth, Edwin, Memorial for Mount Auburn Cemetery, Cambridge, MA (Offsite-box 10)
    - Boston Public Library, Boston, MA (Offsite-box 10)
      Exterior and Interior Photos; Sculpture; Invoice; Photostats of floor plans; Printed Material; Newspaper clippings; see also Large Photos, Box 2
    - Boston Symphony Hall, Boston, MA (Offsite-box 10)
    - Bowdoin College, Brunswick, ME (Offsite-box 10)
      General Photos; Walker Art Gallery; Map; Printed Material
    - Breese, James L., Residence, "The Orchard", Southampton, NY (Offsite-box 10)
      Exterior Photos; Copies of first floor plan
    - Bridgeport, City of, City Hall (proposed), Bridgeport, CT (Offsite-box 10)
      Copy of rendering
    - Bristol National Bank, Bristol, CT (Offsite-box 10)
    - Broadway Cable Company, New York, NY, 1892, 1927-1941 (Offsite-box 10)
      Construction Photos (1892); Copies of renderings; Printed Material (1927-1941)
    - Brooklyn Botanic Gardens, Brooklyn, NY (Offsite-box 11)
      General and Entrance Photos; Copies of renderings; Printed Material
    - Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences, Brooklyn, NY, 1914 (Offsite-box 11)
      Construction photos (1914); Exterior photos; Italian Room photos; Photos of column models; Copies of renderings; Printed Material
    - Brown, Henry W., Residence, Philadelphia, PA (Offsite-box 11)
    - Burke Relief Foundation, White Plains, NY, 1914 (Offsite-box 11)
      Construction photos (1914); Exterior photos; Patient photos; Printed Material; Annual, Biennial Report Documents
    - Burlington, City of, City Hall, Burlington, VT (Offsite-box 11)
      Exterior and Auditorium photos; Photostats of floor plans; Copies of renderings; Printed Material
    - Butler, Joseph G. Jr., Butler Institute of American Art, Youngstown, OH (Offsite-box 12)
      Original Site photo; General photos; Sculpture Models; Copies of renderings; Printed Material
    - Caldwell, E.F., Caldwell and Company Building, Nashville TN (Offsite-box 12)
    - Carnegie Corporation Office, 522 Fifth Ave., New York, NY (Offsite-box 12)
    - Century Association, Century Club, New York, NY (Offsite-box 12)
      Printed Material; see also Large Photos, Box 1
    - Century Holding Company, Apartment House, 998 Fifth Avenue, New York, NY (Offsite-box 12)
      Exterior Photo; Copies of renderings; Printed Material
    - Chapman, Elizabeth Winthrop, Memorial (Offsite-box 12)
    - Chapman Family Tombstones, Bedford, NY (Offsite-box 12)
    - Chateau Lawrence, Bronxville, NY (Offsite-box 12)
    - Cheney, Anne W., Residence, Manchester, CT (Offsite-box 12)
    - Chestnut Hill Pumping Station, Washington, DC (Offsite-box 12)
    - Church of our Lady of Esperanza, New York, NY (Offsite-box 12)
      Exterior photos; Sculpture; Printed Material
    - Church of the Ascension, 36–38 Fifth Avenue, New York, NY (Offsite-box 12)
      Department of Buildings Documents: Parish House and Tower Alterations; Newspaper Clippings
    - City Bank Farmer's Trust Company, New York, NY (Offsite-box 12)
    - Coleman, Samuel, Residence, Newport, RI (Offsite-box 12)
    - Colgate University, Hamilton, NY (Offsite-box 12)
      Copies of renderings of athletic fields; Copies of dormitory floor plans
    - College of Pharmacy, New York, NY (Offsite-box 12)
    - Colony Club, 120-124 Madison Ave., New York, NY (Offsite-box 12)
      Copies of renderings; Newspaper clippings
    - Columbia Trust Co. (Alterations), 60 Broadway, New York, NY (Offsite-box 12)
      Copies of renderings; Department of Buildings documents; Blueprint
    - Columbia University, New York, NY (Box 1 of 3) (Offsite-box 12)
      General: Photos, Copies of blueprints, Photos of 3-dimensional models, Notes; see also Large Photos, Boxes 1 and 2
    - Columbia University, New York, NY (Box 2 of 3) (Offsite-box 13)
      General (cont'd): Copies of renderings; Newspaper Clippings; Printed Material; Publications; Art Building; Business Building: Photos, Department of Buildings (DOB) Documents; Casa Italiana: Photos, Copies of renderings, DOB Documents
    - Columbia University, New York, NY (Box 3 of 3) (Offsite-box 14)
      Chemistry Buildings: Photos, Copies of Renderings; Department of Buildings (DOB) Documents; Faculty House; Fayerweather Hall: DOB Documents; Furnald Hall; John Jay Hall: Photos, Copies of renderings, DOB Documents; Johnson Hall: Photos, Copies of Renderings; Kent Hall: DOB Documents; Physics Building and Laboratory: Photos, Copies of renderings, DOB Documents, Printed Material; President's House: DOB Documents; Schemerhorn Hall: Photos, Copies of renderings, DOB Documents; Women's Dormitory: DOB Documents; Van Amrige Memorial; Sculpture; Proposed 120th Street Buildings: Copies of renderings
    - Commercial National Bank, Shreveport, LA (Offsite-box 14)
      Construction, Interior, and Exterior Photos; Printed Materials
    - Cooper, Peter, Memorial, Cooper Square, New York, NY (Offsite-box 15)
      Correspondence
    - Cowdoin, J.E., Residence, Far Rockaway, NY (Offsite-box 15)
    - Cuban American Sugar Company, Gramercy Refinery, Gramercy, LA (Offsite-box 15)
    - Cutting, Mrs. William Bayard, Memorial, Greenwood Cemetery, Brooklyn, NY (Offsite-box 15)
    - Cutting family, Pedestal of Bronson Cutting Statue, Sante Fe, NM. (Offsite-box 15)
    - De Pauli, Louis, Residence, 527-29 W. 45th St., New York, NY (Offsite-box 15)
    - Detwiler & Co., Brooklyn Tower, Brooklyn, NY (Offsite-box 15)
      Presentation Images
    - Discus Thrower Statue, New York, NY (Offsite-box 15)
    - District National Bank, Washington, DC, 1926 (Offsite-box 15)
      Copies of renderings (1926)
    - Dobbs Building, 618-20 Fifth Ave., New York, NY (Offsite-box 15)
    - Edgar, Commodore William, Residence, Newport, RI (Offsite-box 15)
    - Elks Club Lodge #22, 110 Livingston St., Brooklyn, NY, 1926-1938 (Offsite-box 15)
      Construction Photos (1926-1927); Interior Photos; Elks Head Photos; Copies of Renderings; Printed Material (1929-1938)
    - Farragut Monument, New York, NY (Offsite-box 15)
    - Fayette National Bank, Lexington, KY (Offsite-box 15)
    - Federal National Bank, Washington, DC (Offsite-box 15)
    - Filley, Oliver D., Residence, 684 Park Avenue, New York, NY (Offsite-box 15)
      Blueprint; Department of Buildings Documents
    - First Methodist Episcopal Church, Baltimore, MD (Offsite-box 15)
    - Fisher Company, Tenement at 358-364 East 50th St., New York, NY (Offsite-box 15)
      Tenement House Department Documents
    - Fort Benning Infantry School (Offsite-box 15)
      Printed Material; Academic Building; Chapel; Sculptural Models
    - Apartment building, Forty eight West 57th Street, New York, NY (48 West 57th Street) (Offsite-box 15)
      Copies of renderings
    - Residence, Four West 51st Street, New York, NY (4 West 51st Street) (Offsite-box 15)
    - Four hundred thirty East 57th Street Corporation, tenement housing, New York, NY (430 East 57th Street) (Offsite-box 15)
    - Franklin, Charles C., Residence, Long Branch, NJ (Offsite-box 15)
    - Franklin National Bank, Philadelphia, PA (Offsite-box 15)
      Photos; Printed Material, see also Large Photos, Box 1